I'm home!
Applause
I am the one who looks so big at Takamatsu University, congratulations to all of you!
Because I'm your type, Mr. Takamatsu.
Yay!
LOL!
Boom!
Boom.
Boom. Boom.
Boom-boom.
Music
Oh!
Cute!
LOL!
Thought I'd take a look.
It looks so much prettier since you looked at it.
Eh, it's kind of different at times.
LOL.
It's long.
Oh, wow!
Kagawa Prefecture, everyone says there are stores for samaisuke udon.
There's a category for ordinary stores, Seven, and Seven of Life.
There you go.
Yes, sir.
How many stores do you think there are in Kagawa Prefecture?
How many stores?
You don't know the number problem at all, do you?
Yes, sir.
There are about 380 convenience stores.
That's right.
Do you think there are more or less than these convenience stores?
I think it's a lot.
Yes, I think so.
This number can't be less.
Laughs.
I'll play.
Okay, then. Three choices, 500 points.
A little bit more. 500 points.
Ho
Number two.
Almost double.
Oh!
That's what the circle means.
Seven hundred.
Number three.
1,000 points.
Okay.
Number 1, 500, number 2, 700, first of all, 1000 points.
The big number two, I guess.
Oh, did you know that?
Because I'm the Takamatsu Tourism Ambassador!
What?
LOL!
That's embarrassing!
Don't be embarrassed.
I'll give you my card later.
I have a business card as a tourism ambassador.
I usually take an udon cab.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
It's a cab with udon noodles on it.
Laughs.
Please pay.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for talking to us.
I look forward to working with you again.
thank you
Thank you very much.
That's a good reason, so you're in.
That's great.
I'm kind of more familiar with Takamatsu than I have been since the first radio dominoes.
There's something like that, right?
Yeah.
I'm a little more familiar.
I was just chatting with Mr. Inhuman.
Actually...
It was actually interesting.
Because I was...
Killer.
You're wearing a camo camo.
I'm a tourism ambassador.
I have to do it again.
He's always doing that.
Am I like this?
Is this what I look like?
I hope I see you again.
I'll be careful.
Not at all. Not even in front of Big Cyber.
I don't know what he's saying.
It's the same old thing.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Come here. Come here.
This is the real deal.
Ha-ha-ha.
How long has it been since I've been in Takamatsu?
How many years has it been?
It's been about five years.
It's been five years
It's been five years.
It's been about five years
It's been a long time.
How long has it been since you were here?
Nine years.
Wow.
It's been a long time.
Nice to meet you.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm over here, right?
I'm over here.
I see.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I think we're at the end of our rope.
Yesterday
Here you go.
This is the limit.
Okay, here.
You can go a little further today.
I can't.
Just a little more.
That's all for now.
I look forward to seeing you at the show.
Thank you very much.
thank you for all your help
It's been 9 years
Hmm.
Does that mean I'm 9 years old?
Ha-ha-ha.
Wow, wow, wow.
Don't get me started.
It's just that I'm taking up a lot of space.
I have to take the first one.
Buckwheat noodle shop.
Very good!
Can you say all of Shikoku?
I had a hard time.
I don't know what's wrong.
I don't know.
I don't know.I don't know, I don't know
Shikoku Quiz
I thought it would be bad if I couldn't tell you about Shikoku.
The second one.
Takamatsu.
No, Kagawa.
Kagawa.
The second one.
Kagawa
Ehime
Second one.
Kochi
Tokushima
Oh!
That's great!
I've been using the bathroom lately to memorize some kind of map of Japan.
Right?
It's the same thing as Perorin's.
Oh, man...
He takes her to the bathroom.
Do the same thing.
Wait a minute... it's difficult...
It's hard.
It's free!
Grandpa!
Grandpa.
Grandpa
Is it a video?
Grandpa is so active!
He's doing mikka-minma!
Edit store
Who do you like better, Strawberry or Poco?
Ichigo
Poco Poco
kitten or cat
Which do you like better, Ao or Risa?
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no
They're scary!
Poco with scary eyes
I like Poco more...
I like Poco.
I like Aojyan.
I like Risa too
Bye, Poco.
Today's April Fool's Day.
Thank you.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Maybe when I'm tired.
Look at this.
It's huge.
Famous in Takamatsu.
It's a good luck charm.
This is Ri-chan's...
Let's make it a happy day
Let's make it a happy day!
Let's go!
All right, let's go!
Don't lose your mind.
We're all going to get stronger.
Ready?
Riichan!
I'm home!
I'm back from the first moment of the decoy
and the day of Akasai's simultaneous fall
Thank you for this
I've been thinking
I've been feeling really bitter about it for a long time.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I've been able to wire like this.
I knew it.
I felt like I could say, "Welcome home.
I felt like I could say "I'm home" with pride.
That's why my dad and I
I can say "I'm back in Takamatsu" so loudly.
It was thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
I know it's a lot of work, but...
It was really important
Really important.
That's what emo means.
Thank you so much for coming through for me.
Thank you for today.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for watching.